V1.08 (05/17/2012)
(1) Increase of two versions (free trial version)
   The free version is only effective 16 dot matrix.
   The trial version for all lattice, but will be missing part of the character.
(2) Increase the hotkey function.
(3) Modified multi-lingual generation. H files, the bug does not match the start and end.
(4) Perfect document GuiTool instructions for use, adding more to illustrate.
   Document Download: http://ishare.iask.sina.com.cn/f/24472766.html


v1.07 (05/02/2012)   
   (1) to increase the bdf format encoding filter function, mainly to support the MTK phone dot matrix character.
   (2) Increase the xp control properties.
   (3) increase in the scan mode graphic.
   (4) Modify a bug in bdf bin. (Select the output bitmap, the output of n bitmap file)
   (5) Modified BDF file error when the character display width to 0, save the bitmap (all the characters save a picture) failed.


v1.06 (04/10/2012)
   (1) increase the system font support, easier to operate, fast.
      Enumerate all installed system fonts, you can directly select.

v1.05 (03/24/2012)
   Fontmaker (dot matrix font)
   (1) Fixed character alignment problems.
   (2) a single character or multiple characters output into bitmap file is set.
   (3) improve the Arabic font (unicode font).
   (4) Increase self-defined character function (unicode font).

   Multi-language (multiple languages)
   (1) to increase the output encoding format (mbcs, utf16-lb, the utf8) is set
   (2) increase the array format.

V1.04 (07/16/2011)
   (1) Increase of a string mbcs2unicode (internal codes to Unicode) functions. (Support the transition: the U16-the LE U16-BE, UTF8)

V1.03 (07/05/2011)
   (1) Modify the Example of dot matrix font parsing code more portable. (Basically just modify font_file.c can)
   (2) modify the internal code (MBCS) character dot matrix read an error.
   (3) multi-language support (Simplified Chinese, English), should be improved. . .

V1.02 (07/01/2011)
   1 FontMaker V2.03
     (a) to increase the character aspect ratio adjustment (HorR & VerR)
     (b) to increase support for *. ttc font.
     (c) bdf (bdf) file format to bin file of the Simple Unicode encoding format.

V1.01 (06/29/2011)
   1. FontMaker V2.02
     (a) Simple the Unicode function. (Suitable for small font)
     (b) to increase the scanning direction and the reverse set.
     
   2 Multi-Language V1.01
     (a) modified except for office 2000, and other support.


V1.00: (2007-2011)
   (1) Inherits all the features of the FontMaker V2.01.
   (2) to increase the conversion function of a Multi-Languge V1.00 packaged.